In this clip we are going to be talking more about tea accessories.
Another type of accessory would be a teapot which already comes with the infuser in it.
So you really don't have to buy a separate infuser.
So your tea, buy this teapot and you are all set.
But if you want to go separate ways then you can actually buy an infuser that suits you.
You can buy an infuser a smaller size, that's for a cut that's for 1 teaspoon.
You can buy an infuser if you want to make a pitcher, it's a little bit bigger.
Or if you think your tea is very, very fine then I think you need to buy an infuser which is finer in quality and it's deep down, it's going to steep your tea very nicely.
Besides all these we also have a tea sock which you can use.
This is also very nice, this is a tea sock which also you can use for any kind of tea.
It only changes the color and you have to just wash it with hot water.